[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich", "Newt Gingrich", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "The opening question is, what the hell was wrong with Barack Obama last night?", "question_tokens": ["The", "opening", "question", "is", ",", "what", "the", "hell", "was", "wrong", "with", "Barack", "Obama", "last", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, I'm going to quote the great Newt Gingrich in saying that the man was lying and this is from a previous debate that Newt Gingrich was in with Mitt Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "quote", "the", "great", "Newt", "Gingrich", "in", "saying", "that", "the", "man", "was", "lying", "and", "this", "is", "from", "a", "previous", "debate", "that", "Newt", "Gingrich", "was", "in", "with", "Mitt", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Jennifer Granholm, if Mitt Romney was telling all these lies, why on earth was Barack Obama not correcting them during the debate in front of over 60 million Americans?", "question_tokens": ["Jennifer", "Granholm", ",", "if", "Mitt", "Romney", "was", "telling", "all", "these", "lies", ",", "why", "on", "earth", "was", "Barack", "Obama", "not", "correcting", "them", "during", "the", "debate", "in", "front", "of", "over", "60", "million", "Americans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "IN", "JJ", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "And that's what I would ask, I would love to honestly hear Newt Gingrich's response to this, because as he said in his previous debates, when he had to -- he backed down a bit, you just cannot debate somebody who's dishonest.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "what", "I", "would", "ask", ",", "I", "would", "love", "to", "honestly", "hear", "Newt", "Gingrich", "'s", "response", "to", "this", ",", "because", "as", "he", "said", "in", "his", "previous", "debates", ",", "when", "he", "had", "to", "--", "he", "backed", "down", "a", "bit", ",", "you", "just", "can", "not", "debate", "somebody", "who", "'s", "dishonest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer Granholm", "Mitt Romney", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congressional Budget Office"]}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Was that a fact?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "a", "fact", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "That certainly what the Congressional Budget Office says.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "certainly", "what", "the", "Congressional", "Budget", "Office", "says", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "So in other words, it's not a fact, is it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "in", "other", "words", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "a", "fact", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Wait a second.", "answer_tokens": ["Wait", "a", "second", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mayo Clinic"], "TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Where are you going to find $716 billion and it's not going to be because of Big Bird?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "going", "to", "find", "$", "716", "billion", "and", "it", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "be", "because", "of", "Big", "Bird", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "$", "CD", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "First of all, as Governor Romney pointed out last night, the Mayo Clinic is a private institution run by people privately who do things efficiently, which is very different than the federal government, which has rampant waste.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "as", "Governor", "Romney", "pointed", "out", "last", "night", ",", "the", "Mayo", "Clinic", "is", "a", "private", "institution", "run", "by", "people", "privately", "who", "do", "things", "efficiently", ",", "which", "is", "very", "different", "than", "the", "federal", "government", ",", "which", "has", "rampant", "waste", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$716 billion"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Can he name two, at least two of the deductions that will be cut to be able to pay for the $5 trillion tax cut that Romney is offering?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "he", "name", "two", ",", "at", "least", "two", "of", "the", "deductions", "that", "will", "be", "cut", "to", "be", "able", "to", "pay", "for", "the", "$", "5", "trillion", "tax", "cut", "that", "Romney", "is", "offering", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "$", "CD", "CD", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Very good question.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$5 trillion"], "PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBP", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Can you explain to us any of the detail?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "explain", "to", "us", "any", "of", "the", "detail", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, first of all, there are at least two components to how he ends up paying for the tax cut.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "there", "are", "at", "least", "two", "components", "to", "how", "he", "ends", "up", "paying", "for", "the", "tax", "cut", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "No, he said -- no, absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "said", "--", "no", ",", "absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "-- since he took over is 125,000 jobs?", "question_tokens": ["--", "since", "he", "took", "over", "is", "125,000", "jobs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "I don't know the number exactly but I do know that there's a net gain.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "number", "exactly", "but", "I", "do", "know", "that", "there", "'s", "a", "net", "gain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "How important is the jobs report going to be tomorrow to Barack Obama, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "the", "jobs", "report", "going", "to", "be", "tomorrow", "to", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, we know the jobs report is not going to be good, even if it's better than it has been.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "know", "the", "jobs", "report", "is", "not", "going", "to", "be", "good", ",", "even", "if", "it", "'s", "better", "than", "it", "has", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "-- is you want four more years like this?", "question_tokens": ["--", "is", "you", "want", "four", "more", "years", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Come on.", "answer_tokens": ["Come", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Newt Gingrich, should Big Bird be killed or not?", "question_tokens": ["Newt", "Gingrich", ",", "should", "Big", "Bird", "be", "killed", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "That's total baloney.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "total", "baloney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "So you would save Big Bird?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "would", "save", "Big", "Bird", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Jennifer, yes or no, Big Bird, live or die?", "question_tokens": ["Jennifer", ",", "yes", "or", "no", ",", "Big", "Bird", ",", "live", "or", "die", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Big Bird lives.", "answer_tokens": ["Big", "Bird", "lives", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Is that what you would like to see?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "would", "like", "to", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "I hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I am doing great, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "doing", "great", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "What did you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Denver"]}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "You ever suffer altitude problems?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ever", "suffer", "altitude", "problems", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I've been to Denver many times.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "to", "Denver", "many", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Finally, would you kill Big Bird?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "would", "you", "kill", "Big", "Bird", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Well, as a matter of fact, I voted to kill Big Bird in the past.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "a", "matter", "of", "fact", ",", "I", "voted", "to", "kill", "Big", "Bird", "in", "the", "past", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Can we go back on that one?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "go", "back", "on", "that", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "That was beautifully badly phrased.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "beautifully", "badly", "phrased", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Maria", "Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Crystal, what do you want to say?", "question_tokens": ["Crystal", ",", "what", "do", "you", "want", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I don't know what debate Maria was watching, but President Barack Obama was anything but deft.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "debate", "Maria", "was", "watching", ",", "but", "President", "Barack", "Obama", "was", "anything", "but", "deft", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Has he never seen Mitt Romney debate?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "never", "seen", "Mitt", "Romney", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I think that is a very good question, Piers, because you would think that in talking about the preparation, you would take a look at all of the debates and actually, the one with Newt Gingrich is the one that I think they needed to take a look at, because that's where he eviscerated the Speaker.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "is", "a", "very", "good", "question", ",", "Piers", ",", "because", "you", "would", "think", "that", "in", "talking", "about", "the", "preparation", ",", "you", "would", "take", "a", "look", "at", "all", "of", "the", "debates", "and", "actually", ",", "the", "one", "with", "Newt", "Gingrich", "is", "the", "one", "that", "I", "think", "they", "needed", "to", "take", "a", "look", "at", ",", "because", "that", "'s", "where", "he", "eviscerated", "the", "Speaker", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Biden"]}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "I tend to agree with you, Piers, because Senator Biden is somebody who is a fire brand for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "tend", "to", "agree", "with", "you", ",", "Piers", ",", "because", "Senator", "Biden", "is", "somebody", "who", "is", "a", "fire", "brand", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Who is going to win?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "going", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Crystal, you really think Paul Ryan is going to eviscerate Joe Biden?", "question_tokens": ["Crystal", ",", "you", "really", "think", "Paul", "Ryan", "is", "going", "to", "eviscerate", "Joe", "Biden", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Look, I'm going to put myself out there.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "put", "myself", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan", "Joe Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Yes or no, are you going to run for the presidency again?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "or", "no", ",", "are", "you", "going", "to", "run", "for", "the", "presidency", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "I don't have an answer for you yet because there are a lot of things you have to consider before you make that final decision.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "an", "answer", "for", "you", "yet", "because", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "things", "you", "have", "to", "consider", "before", "you", "make", "that", "final", "decision", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Am I right in thinking you know the answer, you just don't want to give it to me yet?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "in", "thinking", "you", "know", "the", "answer", ",", "you", "just", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "give", "it", "to", "me", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "The issue of great significance that everybody tells me I should just change my mind on and do the politically expedient thing, which is to say that my health care plan was a terrible mistake, I'm not willing to do.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "issue", "of", "great", "significance", "that", "everybody", "tells", "me", "I", "should", "just", "change", "my", "mind", "on", "and", "do", "the", "politically", "expedient", "thing", ",", "which", "is", "to", "say", "that", "my", "health", "care", "plan", "was", "a", "terrible", "mistake", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "willing", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]